adidasoutdoor.com 2019-07-08

# Adidas Five Ten | Privacy Policy

**adidas Outdoor Privacy Policy**

agron, inc., is the exclusive distributor for adidas outdoor and Five Ten in the United States of America. Furthermore, agron inc. _is the operator of adidasoutdoor.com and fiveten.com Website in the United States._   adidasoutdoor.com, fiveten.com, (also referred as "adidas Outdoor," “Five Ten,” "adidas" or "we," "us," or "our") is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information collected at or in connection with the adidas Outdoor website. This Online Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to those adidas Outdoor websites that display or link to this Policy (including adidasoutdoor.com and fiveten.com/us referred to in this Policy as the "Website"). This Policy applies to data collected by adidas Outdoor through its Websites and services that display these terms. It does not apply to those adidas Outdoor sites, services and products that do not display or link to this Policy or that have their privacy policies. This Policy describes the information we collect and how we use it. By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use the Website.

**Consent to Collection and Processing**

This Website may be operated, in whole or in part, from a country other than the United States. By using our Website, you consent to have your personal information transferred to and processed in a jurisdiction outside of the United States.

**What information do we share?**

Our privacy policy is simple: Except as disclosed below, we don't sell, trade, give away, or rent your personal information to any company outside of agron, inc and the adidas Group. One of the basic principles we've tried to follow in designing this Website is to limit the information we collect from and share about you. For further information about the companies within the adidas Group, please visit [http://www.adidas-group.com](http://www.adidas-group.com/).

**Personal Information**

We collect and store information that you provide to our Website or our Customer Service Department or that we receive from third parties (such as companies providing commercially available databases). For example, when you place an order, we collect and store some or all of the following information that you provide: name, billing address, shipping address, email address, telephone number, and credit card number and expiration date adidas Outdoor. We will also collect the following additional information if you choose to provide it when you sign-up for an account: telephone number, gender, personal preferences, social identifier if you choose to log in to your account via social media and age. We collect your e-mail addresses and zip code if you subscribe to our newsletter and we collect your mobile number if you opt in to receive text messages. You may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions located within each newsletter or linked to each text message. We also collect and store your geolocation information. Registration may be required and personal information collected in certain areas of the Website in which you specifically and knowingly provide such information, e.g., community postings (i.e., chat or bulletin boards), suggestions, or customer service requests. When we run a contest or sweepstakes relating to our Website, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. The rules for each contest/sweepstakes will specify how the information gathered from you for entry will be used and disclosed, if it is different than as described in this Policy. Personal information will be collected only if you voluntarily submit it to our sponsors or us.

**Usage Information**

Through your use of our Website, we may also gather certain information about your use of our Website ("Usage Information"). Generally, this information is collected through "traffic data." We collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with our Website. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information, and reference site domain name every time you visit our Website. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve our Website, to provide our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience, and to personalize the Website, our communications with you, and your shopping experience.

**How does adidasoutdoor.com use cookies, advertising, and online tracking?**

Like many websites, we use "cookies," files stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser to identify account holders and to optimize their shopping experience. Cookies also allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves this Website without checking out and send you reminder e-mail about your shopping orders and other shopping opportunities. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so that we can offer you better shopping experience. You may occasionally get cookies from companies advertising on our behalf to tailor advertisements shown to you for goods and services. We do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to our Website. Our systems do not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals, but several of our service providers who utilize these cookies and other tracking technologies on our Website enable you to opt out of this type of advertising. For more information about third party cookies, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp or [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

We use Google Analytics and Google AdWords on the Website to collect Usage Information, to analyze how users use the Website and to provide advertisements to you on other websites.  For more information about how to opt out of having your information used by Google Analytics, visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.  You can learn more about advertising and online tracking and how to opt out of such practices in the paragraph above.

**Interest Based Advertising**

We also use third party companies, including Google Analytics and Google Adwords, to measure and target ads on our behalf about products and services tailored to your interests. We allow these third-party companies to use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags and similar technologies to collect or receive information about your interaction with us on our Website and elsewhere on the internet (“Tracking Data”) and use such Tracking Data to display ads for adidas Outdoor and other companies when you visit this or other websites. These third-party companies may not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals. If you would like to opt out of the collection and use of Tracking Data for ad targeting, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices/.   For more information about how to opt out of having your information used by Google Analytics, visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.

**Is Information collected from children?**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under 13.

**How does adidasoutdoor.com use your personal information?**

We may use your personal information to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, to provide customer service, to provide other services to you, and to personalize the Website, our communications with you, and your shopping experience. For example, when you create an adidas Outdoor account, you can use your account details to log in from any location and on any device. The global single sign-on for your account will allow adidas Outdoor systems to identify you wherever you are, so you will not need to register with us again if you sign in from a different country. Your information also may be used to contact you about sales, new products, new site features, special offers, and personalized offers based on your location, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications. The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from companies within the adidas Group and other companies. We may also combine this information with other information we collect as you interact with our brand across apps, social media and marketing messages we send you. Aggregating data allows adidas Outdoor to update and correct the information contained in our database and to provide you with product recommendations and special offers.

**Third-party Service Providers**

We may hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, credit card processing, shipping, stocking orders, providing customer service, and fraud protection. These service providers have access only to such personal information needed to perform their functions and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of your information. They are restricted from using, selling, distributing or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services. For example, we will share some of your account details (such as your name, email address, password and date of birth) with our cloud service providers for identification and authentication, so you can quickly and efficiently sign-on to your adidas Outdoor account from anywhere in the world.

**Legal and Safety Disclosures**

We may access or disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of adidas Outdoor or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of our Websites and services; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of adidas Outdoor employees, customers or the public.

**Corporate Transactions**

We may disclose personal information as part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets.

**How does adidasoutdoor.com use usage information?**

We use Usage Information to help us determine how people use parts of the Website and who our readers are. This allows us to improve our Website and ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many people as possible. We also use Usage Information to provide statistical "ratings" information in aggregated form to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use the Website.  We may combine Usage Information about you with other information, including Personal Information, about you to personalize the Website and our communications with you and to provide you with information likely to be of interest to you.

**What steps are taken to help secure personal information?**

An athlete can't play without confidence, and you shouldn't order from a company that doesn't follow secure data practices. Our goal is to deliver performance to you in every way. That includes security. Personal information collected at our Website is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. Only those employees and service providers who need access to personal information to do their jobs are allowed access, each having confidentiality obligations. To protect the security of your information during transmission, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. For example, when using a credit card to make an on-line purchase, your personal information is encrypted before you conduct your transaction. Most browsers will give a visual indication of when your connection is secure. For example, Internet Explorer will show a padlock icon in the lower right of the browser window. If you place an order through our Website, you will be asked to set up an account and provide an e-mail address and password. To help protect your personal information, you should be careful about providing your password to others. If you wish to cancel your account, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of your password, please contact Customer Service. Please refer to the last section of this Policy (How to Contact Us) for more information. While we try our best to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**What happens when I link to or from another website?**

Our Website may contain links to other websites. Our Policy does not apply to the practices of other websites, and adidas Outdoor is not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of each website that you visit.

**Can adidasoutdoor.com use information I share in public areas, chat rooms and newsgroups?**

Please remember that any information you share in public areas, such as message boards or feedback sections, becomes public. Our Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any personal information that you expect to keep private.

**How do I opt-out of receiving promotions?**

We provide you with several opportunities to opt-out of receiving our promotional communications and newsletters, including when you set up an account; By clicking on "Manage Your Account" on the Website, and by following the "unsubscribe" opt-out instructions contained in our promotional communications.

**How do I contact you about privacy-related questions?**

If you have questions or comments about our privacy practices, please contact us by e-mail customerservice@adidasoutdoor.com or by mail at the following address:

adidas Outdoor

Attn: Web Administrator

2440 S. Sepulveda Blvd. #201

Los Angeles, CA 90064

If you have a question regarding a product or service, please contact Customer Service by e-mail [customerservice@adidasoutdoor.com](mailto:customerservice@adidasoutdoor.com). 

**What is the Secure Shopping Guarantee?**

We use the industry standard encryption protocol known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to keep your order information secure. We've established a Secure Shopping Guarantee for every transaction that you make with www.adidasoutdoor.com. Should any unauthorized charges appear on your credit card as a result of shopping with www.adidasoutdoor.com, you must notify your credit card provider by its reporting rules and procedures. If you have more questions regarding our policy, you can call one of our Customer Service representatives at 1-800-982-9337 or e-mail us at [customerservice@adidasoutdoor.com](mailto:customerservice@adidasoutdoor.com).

**Applicable Law and Jurisdiction**

California state law governs the interpretation of this Policy and applies to claims for breach of them regardless of conflict of laws principles. Both parties consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in courts sitting in Portland, Oregon. Both parties waive all defenses of lack of personal jurisdiction and forum non conveniens.

**Changes to This Online Privacy Policy**

We will update this Policy as needed to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the bottom. If there are material changes to this Policy or in how adidas Outdoor will use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes before implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to remain informed of how adidas Outdoor is protecting your information.

**Last Updated: May 29, 2018**
